1. callTestCase(findTestCase("main/Actpol_Login_testenv"), [:], STOP_ON_FAILURE)
1. openBrowser("")
5. deleteAllCookies()
9. waitForPageLoad(60)
13. maximizeWindow()
17. ACTPOLTESTENV = 1
21. ACTPOLDEVENV = 2
25. ACTPOLKCENV = 3
29. ACTPOLKBKPCNENV = 4
33. ACTPOLKBKMARENV = 5
37. ACTPOLKMENV = 6
41. ACTPOLKWENV = 7
45. ACTPOLFATKPCNENV = 8
49. ACTPOLFATKMARENV = 9
53. environment = ACTPOLDEVENV
57. Selectenv =
61. switch (environment)
2. println(Selectenv = "ACTPOL-DEV-ENV")
6. navigateToUrl(DEVURL)
10. setText(findTestObject("Actpol_Scripts/login/userid"), username)
14. setMaskedText(findTestObject("Actpol_Scripts/login/password"), password)
18. click(findTestObject("Actpol_Scripts/login/login"))
22. getWindowTitle()
26. delay(5)
30. break
5. markPassed("PASS::Actpol web application login successfully")
9. log = new com.kms.katalon.core.logging.KeywordLogger()
13. selectOptionByValue(findTestObject("Actpol_Scripts/General Search/Algemene Zoekopdracht -test env/Assistentie"), "assist", false)
17. setText(findTestObject("Actpol_Scripts/General Search/Algemene Zoekopdracht -test env/Assistentie Set text"), Generiekassistenite_Module)
21. delay(2)
25. click(findTestObject("Actpol_Scripts/General Search/Algemene Zoekopdracht -test env/Zoeken new"))
29. delay(8)
35. Remember first set default assistentieid after run the script
39. Assistentiexpath = "//*[text()="" + AssistentiedynamicId + ""]/preceding-sibling::td/a[2]"
43. to = findTestObject("Actpol_Scripts/General Search/Algemene Zoekopdracht -test env/View Assistentie")
47. to.addProperty("xpath", EQUALS, Assistentiexpath)
51. println(to)
55. click(to)
59. click(findTestObject("Actpol_Scripts/General Search/Algemene Zoekopdracht -test env/Confirmeren"))
63. delay(12)
67. click(findTestObject("Actpol_Scripts/Generiek/Assistentie/Click roll process"))
71. delay(2)
75. Vreemdelingverify = verifyElementVisible(findTestObject("Object Repository/JIRA/A Relese 6.6/ACTPOL-317/Vreemdeling verify"), OPTIONAL)
79. println(Vreemdelingverify)
83. verify2 = "true"
87. if (Vreemdelingverify == verify2)
1. click(findTestObject("JIRA/A Relese 6.6/ACTPOL-317/Vreemdeling verify"))
5. delay(5)
9. click(findTestObject("Object Repository/JIRA/A Relese 6.6/ACTPOL-317/Vreemdeling tab"))
13. delay(2)
17. click(findTestObject("Object Repository/JIRA/A Relese 6.6/ACTPOL-317/Maatregelen Bewaring tab"))
21. delay(2)
25. click(findTestObject("Object Repository/JIRA/A Relese 6.6/ACTPOL-317/Maatregelen Bewaring tab new"))
29. delay(2)
33. click(findTestObject("Object Repository/JIRA/A Relese 6.6/ACTPOL-317/Maatregelen Bewaring tab new -new"))
37. delay(6)
41. setText(findTestObject("JIRA/A Relese 6.6/ACTPOL-317/Achternaam"), "aa")
45. delay(2)
49. click(findTestObject("JIRA/A Relese 6.6/ACTPOL-317/Achternaam lb 1"))
53. delay(1)
57. click(findTestObject("JIRA/A Relese 6.6/ACTPOL-317/Alcohol gebruik nee"))
61. delay(1)
65. click(findTestObject("JIRA/A Relese 6.6/ACTPOL-317/Drugs gebruik nee"))
69. delay(1)
73. selectOptionByLabel(findTestObject("JIRA/A Relese 6.6/ACTPOL-317/Reden dropdown"), "TER BEWARING", false)
77. delay(1)
81. selectOptionByLabel(findTestObject("JIRA/A Relese 6.6/ACTPOL-317/Type dropdown"), "MAATREGEL EN BEWARING", false)
85. delay(1)
89. click(findTestObject("JIRA/A Relese 6.6/ACTPOL-317/Fouillering nee"))
93. delay(1)
97. click(findTestObject("JIRA/A Relese 6.6/ACTPOL-317/Gebruik handboeien nee"))
101. delay(1)
105. click(findTestObject("JIRA/A Relese 6.6/ACTPOL-317/Gebruik geweld nee"))
109. delay(1)
113. scrollToPosition(10, 7)
117. delay(1)
121. click(findTestObject("JIRA/A Relese 6.6/ACTPOL-317/Verdachte Info tab"))
125. delay(1)
129. click(findTestObject("JIRA/A Relese 6.6/ACTPOL-317/Strafbare feiten"))
133. delay(1)
137. click(findTestObject("JIRA/A Relese 6.6/ACTPOL-317/Strafbare feiten new"))
141. delay(5)
145. selectOptionByLabel(findTestObject("JIRA/A Relese 6.6/ACTPOL-317/Uitvoering 1"), "POGING", false)
149. delay(1)
153. selectOptionByLabel(findTestObject("JIRA/A Relese 6.6/ACTPOL-317/Daderschap"), "MEDEDADER", false)
157. delay(1)
161. selectOptionByLabel(findTestObject("JIRA/A Relese 6.6/ACTPOL-317/Juntu"), "CQ", false)
165. delay(1)
169. click(findTestObject("JIRA/A Relese 6.6/ACTPOL-317/Strafbare feiten new record save"))
173. delay(4)
177. click(findTestObject("JIRA/A Relese 6.6/ACTPOL-317/Maatregel en bewaring save record"))
181. markPassed("PASS::New Tab Maatregelen Bewaring vreemdeling added")