3. Login to the application
1. openBrowser("")
5. deleteAllCookies()
9. waitForPageLoad(60)
13. maximizeWindow()
17. ACTPOLTESTENV = 1
21. ACTPOLDEVENV = 2
25. ACTPOLKCENV = 3
29. ACTPOLKBKPCNENV = 4
33. ACTPOLKBKMARENV = 5
37. ACTPOLKMENV = 6
41. ACTPOLKWENV = 7
45. environment = ACTPOLTESTENV
49. Selectenv =
53. switch (environment)
2. println(Selectenv = "ACTPOL-TEST-ENV")
6. navigateToUrl(TESTURL)
10. setText(findTestObject("Actpol_Scripts/login/userid"), username)
14. setMaskedText(findTestObject("Actpol_Scripts/login/password"), password)
18. click(findTestObject("Actpol_Scripts/login/login"))
22. getWindowTitle()
26. delay(5)
30. break
7. log = new com.kms.katalon.core.logging.KeywordLogger()
11. delay(4)
17. Mouse over to Generic tab
21. log.logInfo("Successfully logged")
25. delay(2)
31. Click MBES tab
35. delay(2)
41. Click MBES tab
45. delay(2)
51. Click MBES tab
55. log.logInfo("Clicking MBES18 tab ")
59. delay(3)
63. takeScreenshot()
67. log.logInfo("MBES18 module is displayed")
71. delay(1)
77. Get text from the feild
81. log.logInfo("Grid is shown contains columns mentioned ::" + optie)
85. delay(1)
91. Get text from the feild
95. log.logInfo("Grid is shown contains columns mentioned ::" + vlg)
99. delay(1)
105. Get text from the feild
109. log.logInfo("Grid is shown contains columns mentioned ::" + datam)
113. delay(1)
119. Get text from the feild
123. log.logInfo("Grid is shown contains columns mentioned ::" + org)
127. delay(1)
133. Get text from the feild
137. log.logInfo("Grid is shown contains columns mentioned ::" + voornaam)
141. delay(1)
147. Get text from the feild
151. log.logInfo("Grid is shown contains columns mentioned ::" + achternaam)
155. delay(1)
161. Get text from the feild
165. log.logInfo("Grid is shown contains columns mentioned ::" + geb)
169. log.logInfo("MBES18 module a grid will shown in Arrestanten, with the Options Vrnummer, Datum incident, Organisatie,Voornaam, Achternaam and  Geboortedatum.")