3. Login to the application
1. openBrowser("")
5. deleteAllCookies()
9. waitForPageLoad(30)
13. maximizeWindow()
17. ACTPOLTESTENV = 1
21. ACTPOLDEVENV = 2
25. ACTPOLKCENV = 3
29. ACTPOLKBKPCNENV = 4
33. ACTPOLKBKMARENV = 5
37. ACTPOLKMENV = 6
41. ACTPOLKWENV = 7
45. environment = ACTPOLDEVENV
49. Selectenv =
53. switch (environment)
2. println(Selectenv = "ACTPOL-DEV-ENV")
6. navigateToUrl(DEVURL)
10. setText(findTestObject("Actpol_Scripts/login/userid"), username)
14. setMaskedText(findTestObject("Actpol_Scripts/login/password"), password)
18. click(findTestObject("Actpol_Scripts/login/login"))
22. getWindowTitle()
26. break
7. log = new com.kms.katalon.core.logging.KeywordLogger()
13. Mouse over to opsporing
17. log.logInfo("Successfully logged")
21. delay(2)
27. Click MBES tab
31. log.logInfo("Clicking MBES18 tab ")
35. delay(1)
41. Mouse over to Generic tab
45. delay(8)
51. Click new btn
55. log.logInfo("Clicking MBES18 new button ")
59. delay(6)
65. Click new btn in Registratie
69. delay(1)
75. Select required dropdown fro the list
79. delay(1)
85. Select required dropdown fro the list
89. delay(1)
95. Select required dropdown fro the list
99. delay(1)
105. Select required dropdown fro the list
109. delay(1)
115. Enter the text from the feild
119. delay(1)
125. Enter the text from the feild
129. delay(1)
135. Enter the text from the feild
139. delay(1)
145. Enter the date
149. delay(1)
155. Click save btn
159. delay(1)
165. Click on Registratie tab
169. delay(1)
175. Click on Personalia tab
179. delay(2)
183. setText(findTestObject("Actpol_Scripts/Opsporing/MBES18/2 Personalia/Achternaam text"), "aa")
187. delay(2)
191. click(findTestObject("Actpol_Scripts/Opsporing/MBES18/2 Personalia/Achternaam text lb"))