3. Login to the application
1. openBrowser("")
5. deleteAllCookies()
9. waitForPageLoad(30)
13. maximizeWindow()
17. ACTPOLTESTENV = 1
21. ACTPOLDEVENV = 2
25. ACTPOLKCENV = 3
29. ACTPOLKBKPCNENV = 4
33. ACTPOLKBKMARENV = 5
37. ACTPOLKMENV = 6
41. ACTPOLKWENV = 7
45. environment = ACTPOLDEVENV
49. Selectenv =
53. switch (environment)
2. println(Selectenv = "ACTPOL-DEV-ENV")
6. navigateToUrl(DEVURL)
10. setText(findTestObject("Actpol_Scripts/login/userid"), username)
14. setMaskedText(findTestObject("Actpol_Scripts/login/password"), password)
18. click(findTestObject("Actpol_Scripts/login/login"))
22. getWindowTitle()
26. break
7. log = new com.kms.katalon.core.logging.KeywordLogger()
13. Mouse over to opsporing
17. log.logInfo("Successfully logged")
21. delay(2)
27. Click MBES tab
31. log.logInfo("Clicking MBES18 tab ")
35. delay(1)
41. Mouse over to Generic tab
45. delay(8)
51. Click new btn
55. log.logInfo("Clicking MBES18 new button ")
59. delay(6)
65. Click new btn in Registratie