3. Login to the application
1. openBrowser("")
5. deleteAllCookies()
9. waitForPageLoad(60)
13. maximizeWindow()
17. ACTPOLTESTENV = 1
21. ACTPOLDEVENV = 2
25. ACTPOLKCENV = 3
29. ACTPOLKBKPCNENV = 4
33. ACTPOLKBKMARENV = 5
37. ACTPOLKMENV = 6
41. ACTPOLKWENV = 7
45. environment = ACTPOLTESTENV
49. Selectenv =
53. switch (environment)
2. println(Selectenv = "ACTPOL-TEST-ENV")
6. navigateToUrl(TESTURL)
10. setText(findTestObject("Actpol_Scripts/login/userid"), username)
14. setMaskedText(findTestObject("Actpol_Scripts/login/password"), password)
18. click(findTestObject("Actpol_Scripts/login/login"))
22. getWindowTitle()
26. delay(5)
30. break
7. log = new com.kms.katalon.core.logging.KeywordLogger()
11. delay(1)
17. Mouse over to Generic tab
21. log.logInfo("Successfully logged")
25. delay(2)
31. Click MBES tab
35. delay(2)
41. Click MBES tab
45. log.logInfo("Clicking MBES18 tab ")
49. delay(1)
53. delay(8)
59. Click new btn
63. log.logInfo("Clicking MBES18 new button ")
67. delay(6)
73. Click new btn in Registratie
77. delay(1)
83. Select required dropdown fro the list
87. delay(1)
93. Select required dropdown fro the list
97. delay(1)
103. Select required dropdown fro the list
107. delay(1)
113. Select required dropdown fro the list
117. delay(1)
123. Enter the text from the feild
127. delay(1)
133. Enter the text from the feild
137. delay(1)
143. Enter the text from the feild
147. delay(1)
153. Enter the date
157. click(findTestObject("Actpol_Scripts/Opsporing/MBES18/1 Registratie/Datum calendar icon"))
161. delay(2)
165. selectOptionByLabel(findTestObject("Actpol_Scripts/Monthyear/Rightmonth"), "sep", false)
169. delay(1)
173. selectOptionByLabel(findTestObject("Actpol_Scripts/Monthyear/Rightyear"), "2019", false)
177. delay(1)
181. click(findTestObject("Actpol_Scripts/Date/16th right frame"))
185. delay(1)
191. Click save btn
195. delay(1)
201. Click on Registratie tab
205. delay(1)
211. Click on Personalia tab
215. delay(2)
221. Click Save tab
225. delay(1)
231. Checking Error message personalia tab
235. achternaamverify = "Dit is een vereiste veld"
239. log.logInfo(Achternaam)
243. if (Achternaam == achternaamverify)
1. log.logInfo("success and error message in Achternaam")
247. delay(2)
253. Checking Error message personalia tab
257. Garantstellerverify = "Dit is een vereiste veld"
261. log.logInfo(Garantsteller)
265. if (Garantsteller == Garantstellerverify)
1. log.logInfo("success and error message in Garantsteller/referent")
269. delay(2)
273. comment("Checking button how it is working")
279. Click Achternaam new btn
283. delay(4)
289. Select default persoon
293. delay(2)
299. Click close btn
303. delay(2)
307. comment("Checking text box how it is working")
313. Enter text from the feild
317. delay(2)
323. Select required dropdown
327. comment("Checking edit btn how it is working")
331. delay(1)
337. Click edit btn
341. delay(6)
347. Enter text from the feild
351. delay(1)
357. Click save btn
361. delay(4)
365. comment("Checking Search btn how it is working")
371. Click Search btn
375. delay(1)
381. Move to position
385. delay(4)
391. Click on close btn
395. delay(6)
401. Enter text from the feild
405. delay(2)
411. Select required dropdown
415. delay(1)
421. Click on Personalia tab
425. delay(1)
431. Click save btn