3. Login to the application
1. openBrowser("")
5. deleteAllCookies()
9. waitForPageLoad(60)
13. maximizeWindow()
17. ACTPOLTESTENV = 1
21. ACTPOLDEVENV = 2
25. ACTPOLKCENV = 3
29. ACTPOLKBKPCNENV = 4
33. ACTPOLKBKMARENV = 5
37. ACTPOLKMENV = 6
41. ACTPOLKWENV = 7
45. environment = ACTPOLTESTENV
49. Selectenv =
53. switch (environment)
2. println(Selectenv = "ACTPOL-TEST-ENV")
6. navigateToUrl(TESTURL)
10. setText(findTestObject("Actpol_Scripts/login/userid"), username)
14. setMaskedText(findTestObject("Actpol_Scripts/login/password"), password)
18. click(findTestObject("Actpol_Scripts/login/login"))
22. getWindowTitle()
26. delay(5)
30. break
7. log = new com.kms.katalon.core.logging.KeywordLogger()
13. Mouse over to Generic tab
17. log.logInfo("Successfully logged")
21. delay(2)
27. Click MBES tab
31. delay(2)
37. Click MBES tab
41. log.logInfo("Clicking MBES18 tab ")
45. delay(1)
49. delay(8)
55. Click new btn
59. log.logInfo("Clicking MBES18 new button ")
63. delay(6)
69. Click new btn in Registratie
73. delay(1)
79. Select required dropdown fro the list
83. delay(1)
89. Select required dropdown fro the list
93. delay(1)
99. Select required dropdown fro the list
103. delay(1)
109. Select required dropdown fro the list
113. delay(1)
119. Enter the text from the feild