3. Login to the application
1. openBrowser("")
5. deleteAllCookies()
9. waitForPageLoad(30)
13. maximizeWindow()
17. ACTPOLTESTENV = 1
21. ACTPOLDEVENV = 2
25. ACTPOLKCENV = 3
29. ACTPOLKBKPCNENV = 4
33. ACTPOLKBKMARENV = 5
37. ACTPOLKMENV = 6
41. ACTPOLKWENV = 7
45. environment = ACTPOLDEVENV
49. Selectenv =
53. switch (environment)
2. println(Selectenv = "ACTPOL-DEV-ENV")
6. navigateToUrl(DEVURL)
10. setText(findTestObject("Actpol_Scripts/login/userid"), username)
14. setMaskedText(findTestObject("Actpol_Scripts/login/password"), password)
18. click(findTestObject("Actpol_Scripts/login/login"))
22. getWindowTitle()
26. break
7. log = new com.kms.katalon.core.logging.KeywordLogger()
13. Mouse over to opsporing
17. log.logInfo("Successfully logged")
21. delay(2)
27. Click MBES tab
31. log.logInfo("Clicking MBES18 tab ")
35. delay(1)
41. Mouse over to Generic tab
45. delay(3)
49. takeScreenshot()
53. log.logInfo("MBES18 module is displayed")
57. delay(1)
63. Get text from the feild
67. log.logInfo("Grid is shown contains columns mentioned ::" + optie)
71. delay(1)
77. Get text from the feild
81. log.logInfo("Grid is shown contains columns mentioned ::" + vlg)
85. delay(1)
91. Get text from the feild
95. log.logInfo("Grid is shown contains columns mentioned ::" + datam)
99. delay(1)
105. Get text from the feild
109. log.logInfo("Grid is shown contains columns mentioned ::" + bij)
113. delay(1)
119. Get text from the feild
123. log.logInfo("Grid is shown contains columns mentioned ::" + org)
127. delay(1)
133. Get text from the feild
137. log.logInfo("Grid is shown contains columns mentioned ::" + con)
141. delay(1)
147. Get text from the feild
151. log.logInfo("Grid is shown contains columns mentioned ::" + telefoon)
155. delay(1)
161. Get text from the feild
165. log.logInfo("Grid is shown contains columns mentioned ::" + voornaam)
169. delay(1)
175. Get text from the feild
179. log.logInfo("Grid is shown contains columns mentioned ::" + achternaam)
183. delay(1)
189. Get text from the feild
193. log.logInfo("Grid is shown contains columns mentioned ::" + geb)