3. Login to the application
1. openBrowser("")
5. deleteAllCookies()
9. waitForPageLoad(30)
13. maximizeWindow()
17. ACTPOLTESTENV = 1
21. ACTPOLDEVENV = 2
25. ACTPOLKCENV = 3
29. ACTPOLKBKPCNENV = 4
33. ACTPOLKBKMARENV = 5
37. ACTPOLKMENV = 6
41. ACTPOLKWENV = 7
45. environment = ACTPOLDEVENV
49. Selectenv =
53. switch (environment)
2. println(Selectenv = "ACTPOL-DEV-ENV")
6. navigateToUrl(DEVURL)
10. setText(findTestObject("Actpol_Scripts/login/userid"), username)
14. setMaskedText(findTestObject("Actpol_Scripts/login/password"), password)
18. click(findTestObject("Actpol_Scripts/login/login"))
22. getWindowTitle()
26. break
7. log = new com.kms.katalon.core.logging.KeywordLogger()
13. Mouse over to opsporing
17. log.logInfo("Successfully logged")
21. delay(2)
27. Click MBES tab
31. log.logInfo("Clicking MBES18 tab ")
35. delay(1)
41. Mouse over to Generic tab
45. delay(5)
51. Click new btn
55. log.logInfo("Clicking MBES18 new button ")
59. delay(1)
63. takeScreenshot()
67. delay(1)
71. comment("Checking This should contain tab registratie, Personalia, Inbewaringstellings c.q. Plaatsingegevens, Gedrag/Medisch, Incidenten, Overige gegevens, Bezittingen/Bagage, Documenten. ")
77. Registration tab is visible in in the grid.
81. log.logInfo("Grid is shown contains tabs mentioned ::" + reg)
85. delay(1)
91. Personalia tab is visible in in the grid.
95. log.logInfo("Grid is shown contains columns mentioned ::" + per)
99. delay(1)
105. INBEWARINGSTELLINGS C.Q. PLAATSINGSGEGEVENS tab is visible in in the grid.
109. log.logInfo("Grid is shown contains columns mentioned ::" + inb)
113. delay(1)
119. GEDRAG/MEDISCH tab is visible in in the grid.
123. log.logInfo("Grid is shown contains columns mentioned ::" + ged)
127. delay(1)
133. INCIDENTEN tab is visible in in the grid.
137. log.logInfo("Grid is shown contains columns mentioned ::" + inc)
141. delay(1)
147. OVERIGE GEGEVENS tab is visible in in the grid.
151. log.logInfo("Grid is shown contains columns mentioned ::" + over)
155. delay(1)
161. BEZITTINGEN/BAGAGE tab is visible in in the grid.
165. log.logInfo("Grid is shown contains columns mentioned ::" + begi)
169. delay(1)
173. comment("Data entering in Registratie tab")
177. delay(1)
183. Click new btn in Registratie
187. delay(1)
193. Click save btn
197. delay(3)
201. takeScreenshot()
205. log.logInfo("without throwing error data is saved the grid...")
209. log.logInfo("not getting error message")
215. Click new btn in Registratie
219. delay(1)
225. Select required dropdown fro the list
229. delay(1)
235. Select required dropdown fro the list
239. delay(1)
245. Select required dropdown fro the list
249. delay(1)
255. Select required dropdown fro the list
259. delay(1)
265. Enter the text from the feild
269. delay(1)
275. Enter the text from the feild
279. delay(1)
285. Enter the text from the feild
289. delay(1)
295. Enter the date
299. delay(1)
305. Click save btn
309. delay(1)
313. takeScreenshot()
317. delay(1)
321. comment("Editing existing record in Registratie")
327. Edit the existing record
331. delay(2)
337. Select required dropdown fro the list
341. delay(1)
347. Select required dropdown fro the list
351. delay(1)
357. Select required dropdown fro the list
361. delay(1)
367. Select required dropdown fro the list
371. delay(1)
377. Select required dropdown fro the list
381. delay(1)
387. Enter the text from the feild
391. delay(1)
397. Enter the text from the feild
401. delay(1)
407. Enter the date
411. delay(1)
417. Click save btn
421. log.logInfo("edit mode working fine ")
425. delay(1)
429. comment("View existing record in Registratie")
433. delay(1)
439. Click view mode for existing saved record
443. log.logInfo("View mode is displaying new button ")
447. delay(1)
451. takeScreenshot()
455. delay(1)
461. Click the close btn
465. delay(1)
469. comment("View existing record in Registratie")
473. delay(1)
479. Click delete btn
483. delay(1)
489. Re conform the delete btn
493. delay(1)
497. takeScreenshot()
501. delay(1)
505. click(findTestObject("Actpol_Scripts/Opsporing/MBES18/1 Registratie/registratie tab"))