3. Login to the application
1. openBrowser("")
5. deleteAllCookies()
9. waitForPageLoad(30)
13. maximizeWindow()
17. ACTPOLTESTENV = 1
21. ACTPOLDEVENV = 2
25. ACTPOLKCENV = 3
29. ACTPOLKBKPCNENV = 4
33. ACTPOLKBKMARENV = 5
37. ACTPOLKMENV = 6
41. ACTPOLKWENV = 7
45. environment = ACTPOLDEVENV
49. Selectenv =
53. switch (environment)
2. println(Selectenv = "ACTPOL-DEV-ENV")
6. navigateToUrl(DEVURL)
10. setText(findTestObject("Actpol_Scripts/login/userid"), username)
14. setMaskedText(findTestObject("Actpol_Scripts/login/password"), password)
18. click(findTestObject("Actpol_Scripts/login/login"))
22. getWindowTitle()
26. break
7. log = new com.kms.katalon.core.logging.KeywordLogger()
13. Mouse over to opsporing
17. log.logInfo("Successfully logged")
21. delay(2)
27. Click MBES tab
31. log.logInfo("Clicking MBES18 tab ")
35. delay(1)
41. Mouse over to Generic tab
45. delay(8)
51. Click new btn
55. log.logInfo("Clicking MBES18 new button ")
59. delay(6)
65. Click new btn in Registratie
69. delay(1)
75. Select required dropdown fro the list
79. delay(1)
85. Select required dropdown fro the list
89. delay(1)
95. Select required dropdown fro the list
99. delay(1)
105. Select required dropdown fro the list
109. delay(1)
115. Enter the text from the feild
119. delay(1)
125. Enter the text from the feild
129. delay(1)
135. Enter the text from the feild
139. delay(1)
145. Enter the date
149. delay(1)
155. Click save btn
159. delay(1)
165. Click on Registratie tab
169. delay(1)
175. Click on Personalia tab
179. delay(2)
185. Click Save tab
189. delay(1)
195. Checking Error message personalia tab
199. achternaamverify = "Dit is een vereiste veld"
203. log.logInfo(Achternaam)
207. if (Achternaam == achternaamverify)
1. log.logInfo("success and error message in Achternaam")
211. delay(2)
217. Checking Error message personalia tab
221. Garantstellerverify = "Dit is een vereiste veld"
225. log.logInfo(Garantsteller)
229. if (Garantsteller == Garantstellerverify)
1. log.logInfo("success and error message in Garantsteller/referent")
233. delay(2)
237. comment("Checking button how it is working")
243. Click Achternaam new btn
247. delay(4)
253. Select default persoon
257. delay(2)
263. Click close btn
267. delay(2)
271. comment("Checking text box how it is working")
277. Enter text from the feild
281. delay(2)
287. Select required dropdown
291. comment("Checking edit btn how it is working")
295. delay(1)
301. Click edit btn
305. delay(6)
311. Enter text from the feild
315. delay(1)
321. Click save btn
325. delay(4)
329. comment("Checking Search btn how it is working")
335. Click Search btn
339. delay(1)
345. Move to position
349. delay(4)
355. Click on close btn
359. delay(6)
365. Enter text from the feild
369. delay(2)
375. Select required dropdown
379. delay(1)
385. Click on Personalia tab
389. delay(1)
395. Click save btn