1. callTestCase(findTestCase("main/Actpol_Login_testenv"), [:], STOP_ON_FAILURE)
1. openBrowser("")
5. deleteAllCookies()
9. waitForPageLoad(60)
13. maximizeWindow()
17. ACTPOLTESTENV = 1
21. ACTPOLDEVENV = 2
25. ACTPOLKCENV = 3
29. ACTPOLKBKPCNENV = 4
33. ACTPOLKBKMARENV = 5
37. ACTPOLKMENV = 6
41. ACTPOLKWENV = 7
45. ACTPOLFATKPCNENV = 8
49. ACTPOLFATKMARENV = 9
53. environment = ACTPOLTESTENV
57. Selectenv =
61. switch (environment)
2. println(Selectenv = "ACTPOL-TEST-ENV")
6. navigateToUrl(TESTURL)
10. setText(findTestObject("Actpol_Scripts/login/userid"), username)
14. setMaskedText(findTestObject("Actpol_Scripts/login/password"), password)
18. click(findTestObject("Actpol_Scripts/login/login"))
22. getWindowTitle()
26. delay(5)
30. break
5. markPassed("PASS::Actpol web application login successfully")
9. log = new com.kms.katalon.core.logging.KeywordLogger()
13. selectOptionByValue(findTestObject("Actpol_Scripts/General Search/Algemene Zoekopdracht -test env/Assistentie"), "assist", false)
17. setText(findTestObject("Actpol_Scripts/General Search/Algemene Zoekopdracht -test env/Assistentie Set text"), Generiekassistenite_Module)
21. delay(2)
25. click(findTestObject("Actpol_Scripts/General Search/Algemene Zoekopdracht -test env/Zoeken new"))
29. delay(8)
35. Remember first set default assistentieid after run the script
39. Assistentiexpath = "//*[text()="" + AssistentiedynamicId + ""]/preceding-sibling::td/a[2]"
43. to = findTestObject("Actpol_Scripts/General Search/Algemene Zoekopdracht -test env/View Assistentie")
47. to.addProperty("xpath", EQUALS, Assistentiexpath)
51. println(to)
55. click(to)
59. click(findTestObject("Actpol_Scripts/General Search/Algemene Zoekopdracht -test env/Confirmeren"))
63. delay(12)
67. click(findTestObject("Actpol_Scripts/Generiek/Assistentie/Click roll process"))
71. delay(2)
75. Vreemdelingverify = verifyElementVisible(findTestObject("Object Repository/JIRA/A Relese 6.6/ACTPOL-317/Vreemdeling verify"), OPTIONAL)
79. log.logInfo(Vreemdelingverify)
83. verify2 = "true"
87. if (Vreemdelingverify == verify2)
1. click(findTestObject("JIRA/A Relese 6.6/ACTPOL-317/Vreemdeling verify"))
5. delay(5)
9. click(findTestObject("Object Repository/JIRA/A Relese 6.6/ACTPOL-317/Vreemdeling tab"))
13. delay(2)
17. click(findTestObject("Object Repository/JIRA/A Relese 6.6/ACTPOL-317/Toegang"))
21. delay(5)
25. scrollToElement(findTestObject("Object Repository/JIRA/A Relese 6.6/ACTPOL-317/Voorwaarde toegang new"), 3)
29. delay(2)
33. Opleggingverify = verifyElementVisible(findTestObject("JIRA/A Relese 6.6/ACTPOL-317/ver verify text"), OPTIONAL)
37. log.logInfo(Opleggingverify)
41. delay(2)
45. Overleggingverify = verifyElementVisible(findTestObject("JIRA/A Relese 6.6/ACTPOL-320/320 VER verify text"), OPTIONAL)
49. log.logInfo(Overleggingverify)
53. recheck = "true"
57. delay(2)
61. if (Opleggingverify == recheck && Overleggingverify == recheck)
1. logInfo("Both dropdowns are already configured")
5. log.logInfo("both dropdown already existing in the grid")
9. markPassed("PASS::oplegging van de plicht van 72 uren is visible")
13. markPassed("PASS::Overlegging van een garantverklaring, ondertekend door is visible")
17. delay(2)