1. callTestCase(findTestCase("main/Actpol_Login_testenv"), [:], STOP_ON_FAILURE)
1. openBrowser("")
5. deleteAllCookies()
9. waitForPageLoad(30)
13. maximizeWindow()
17. ACTPOLTESTENV = 1
21. ACTPOLDEVENV = 2
25. ACTPOLKCENV = 3
29. ACTPOLKBKPCNENV = 4
33. ACTPOLKBKMARENV = 5
37. ACTPOLKMENV = 6
41. ACTPOLKWENV = 7
45. environment = ACTPOLTESTENV
49. Selectenv =
53. switch (environment)
2. println(Selectenv = "ACTPOL-TEST-ENV")
6. navigateToUrl(TESTURL)
10. setText(findTestObject("Actpol_Scripts/login/userid"), username)
14. setMaskedText(findTestObject("Actpol_Scripts/login/password"), password)
18. click(findTestObject("Actpol_Scripts/login/login"))
22. getWindowTitle()
26. break
5. selectOptionByValue(findTestObject("Actpol_Scripts/General Search/Algemene Zoekopdracht -test env/Assistentie"), "assist", false)
9. setText(findTestObject("Actpol_Scripts/General Search/Algemene Zoekopdracht -test env/Assistentie Set text"), Generiekassistenite_Module)
13. delay(2)
17. click(findTestObject("Actpol_Scripts/General Search/Algemene Zoekopdracht -test env/Zoeken new"))
21. delay(2)
27. Remember first set default assistentieid after run the script
31. Assistentiexpath = "//*[text()="" + AssistentiedynamicId + ""]/preceding-sibling::td/a[2]"
35. to = findTestObject("Actpol_Scripts/General Search/Algemene Zoekopdracht -test env/View Assistentie")
39. to.addProperty("xpath", EQUALS, Assistentiexpath)
43. delay(5)
47. click(to)
51. delay(2)
55. click(findTestObject("Actpol_Scripts/General Search/Algemene Zoekopdracht -test env/Confirmeren"))
59. delay(5)
63. click(findTestObject("Actpol_Scripts/Generiek/Assistentie/Click roll process"))
67. delay(2)
71. click(findTestObject("Actpol_Scripts/Generiek/Assistentie/Click new process"))
75. delay(2)
79. comment("Select process "BETROKKEN VAARTUIG"")
85. Select required dropdown
89. delay(3)
95. Click Contacten tab
99. delay(1)
105. Click Vaartuig tab
109. delay(2)
115. Click Vaartuig  new btn
119. delay(4)
125. Click new Vaartuig  tab
129. delay(1)
135. Click Opvarende tab
139. delay(2)
145. Click Opvarende new
149. delay(4)
155. enter text from the feild :: toevoegen inzittende
159. delay(2)
165. Select required dropdown
169. delay(1)
175. Click save btn
179. delay(1)
183. takeScreenshot()
187. delay(1)
193. Select required drop down :: Bemaningslid ja
197. delay(2)
203. Select required drop down :: Bemaningslid Nee
207. delay(2)
213. Enter text from the feild :: toevoegen inzittende Naam 2
217. delay(2)
223. Select required dropdown
227. delay(1)
233. Click save btn
237. delay(1)
241. scrollToPosition(10, 7)
245. delay(1)
249. takeScreenshot()