3. Login to the application
1. openBrowser("")
5. deleteAllCookies()
9. waitForPageLoad(60)
13. maximizeWindow()
17. ACTPOLTESTENV = 1
21. ACTPOLDEVENV = 2
25. ACTPOLKCENV = 3
29. ACTPOLKBKPCNENV = 4
33. ACTPOLKBKMARENV = 5
37. ACTPOLKMENV = 6
41. ACTPOLKWENV = 7
45. environment = ACTPOLTESTENV
49. Selectenv =
53. switch (environment)
2. println(Selectenv = "ACTPOL-TEST-ENV")
6. navigateToUrl(TESTURL)
10. setText(findTestObject("Actpol_Scripts/login/userid"), username)
14. setMaskedText(findTestObject("Actpol_Scripts/login/password"), password)
18. click(findTestObject("Actpol_Scripts/login/login"))
22. getWindowTitle()
26. delay(5)
30. break
7. log = new com.kms.katalon.core.logging.KeywordLogger()
11. delay(1)
17. Mouse over to Generic tab
21. log.logInfo("Successfully logged")
25. delay(3)
31. Click MBES tab
35. delay(2)
41. Click MBES tab
45. log.logInfo("Clicking MBES18 tab ")
49. delay(1)
53. delay(5)
59. Click new btn
63. log.logInfo("Clicking MBES18 new button ")
67. delay(1)
71. takeScreenshot()
75. delay(1)
79. comment("Checking This should contain tab registratie, Personalia, Inbewaringstellings c.q. Plaatsingegevens, Gedrag/Medisch, Incidenten, Overige gegevens, Bezittingen/Bagage, Documenten. ")
85. Registration tab is visible in in the grid.
89. log.logInfo("Grid is shown contains tabs mentioned ::" + reg)
93. delay(1)
99. Personalia tab is visible in in the grid.
103. log.logInfo("Grid is shown contains columns mentioned ::" + per)
107. delay(1)
113. INBEWARINGSTELLINGS C.Q. PLAATSINGSGEGEVENS tab is visible in in the grid.
117. log.logInfo("Grid is shown contains columns mentioned ::" + inb)
121. delay(1)
127. GEDRAG/MEDISCH tab is visible in in the grid.
131. log.logInfo("Grid is shown contains columns mentioned ::" + ged)
135. delay(1)
141. INCIDENTEN tab is visible in in the grid.
145. log.logInfo("Grid is shown contains columns mentioned ::" + inc)
149. delay(1)
155. OVERIGE GEGEVENS tab is visible in in the grid.
159. log.logInfo("Grid is shown contains columns mentioned ::" + over)
163. delay(1)
169. BEZITTINGEN/BAGAGE tab is visible in in the grid.
173. log.logInfo("Grid is shown contains columns mentioned ::" + begi)
177. delay(1)
181. comment("Data entering in Registratie tab")
185. delay(1)
191. Click new btn in Registratie
195. delay(1)
201. Click save btn
205. delay(1)
209. getAlertText()
213. delay(1)
217. acceptAlert()
221. delay(3)
225. takeScreenshot()
229. log.logInfo("without throwing error data is saved the grid...")
233. log.logInfo("not getting error message")
239. Click new btn in Registratie
243. delay(1)
247. selectOptionByValue(findTestObject("Object Repository/temp/Page_ACTPOL Test/select_KORPS POLITIE CURACAOOPENBARE MINISTERIEAMBULANCESKSBRANDWEER"), "1", true)
253. Select required dropdown fro the list
257. delay(1)
263. Select required dropdown fro the list
267. delay(1)
273. Select required dropdown fro the list
277. delay(1)
283. Select required dropdown fro the list
287. delay(1)
293. Enter the text from the feild
297. delay(1)
303. Enter the text from the feild
307. delay(1)
313. Enter the text from the feild
317. delay(1)
323. Enter the date
327. click(findTestObject("Actpol_Scripts/Opsporing/MBES18/1 Registratie/Datum calendar icon"))
331. delay(2)
335. selectOptionByLabel(findTestObject("Actpol_Scripts/Monthyear/Rightmonth"), "sep", false)
339. delay(1)
343. selectOptionByLabel(findTestObject("Actpol_Scripts/Monthyear/Rightyear"), "2019", false)
347. delay(1)
351. click(findTestObject("Actpol_Scripts/Date/16th right frame"))
355. delay(1)
361. Click save btn
365. delay(1)
369. takeScreenshot()
373. delay(1)
377. comment("Editing existing record in Registratie")
383. Edit the existing record
387. delay(2)
393. Select required dropdown fro the list
397. delay(1)
403. Select required dropdown fro the list
407. delay(1)
413. Select required dropdown fro the list
417. delay(1)
423. Select required dropdown fro the list
427. delay(1)
433. Select required dropdown fro the list
437. delay(1)
443. Enter the text from the feild
447. delay(1)
453. Enter the text from the feild
457. delay(1)
463. Enter the date
467. delay(1)
473. Click save btn
477. log.logInfo("edit mode working fine ")
481. delay(1)
485. comment("View existing record in Registratie")
489. delay(1)
495. Click view mode for existing saved record
499. log.logInfo("View mode is displaying new button ")
503. delay(1)
507. takeScreenshot()
511. delay(1)
517. Click the close btn
521. delay(1)
525. comment("View existing record in Registratie")
529. delay(1)
535. Click delete btn
539. delay(1)
545. Re conform the delete btn
549. delay(1)
553. takeScreenshot()
557. delay(1)
561. click(findTestObject("Actpol_Scripts/Opsporing/MBES18/1 Registratie/registratie tab"))