1. callTestCase(findTestCase("main/Actpol_Login_testenv"), [:], STOP_ON_FAILURE)
1. openBrowser("")
5. deleteAllCookies()
9. waitForPageLoad(30)
13. maximizeWindow()
17. ACTPOLTESTENV = 1
21. ACTPOLDEVENV = 2
25. ACTPOLKCENV = 3
29. ACTPOLKBKPCNENV = 4
33. ACTPOLKBKMARENV = 5
37. ACTPOLKMENV = 6
41. ACTPOLKWENV = 7
45. environment = ACTPOLDEVENV
49. Selectenv =
53. switch (environment)
2. println(Selectenv = "ACTPOL-DEV-ENV")
6. navigateToUrl(DEVURL)
10. setText(findTestObject("Actpol_Scripts/login/userid"), username)
14. setMaskedText(findTestObject("Actpol_Scripts/login/password"), password)
18. click(findTestObject("Actpol_Scripts/login/login"))
22. getWindowTitle()
26. break
5. mouseOver(findTestObject("Actpol_Scripts/Menu navigation/Opsporing/Opsporing"))
9. delay(1)
13. click(findTestObject("Actpol_Scripts/Opsporing/MBES18/MBES18 TAB"))
17. comment("Adding all feilds of MBES18 ")
21. delay(2)
25. click(findTestObject("Actpol_Scripts/Opsporing/MBES18/10 MBES search module/Datum Incident Calender icon"))
29. delay(2)
33. selectOptionByLabel(findTestObject("Actpol_Scripts/Monthyear/Leftmonth"), "sep", false)
37. delay(1)
41. selectOptionByLabel(findTestObject("Actpol_Scripts/Monthyear/Leftyear"), "2019", false)
45. delay(1)
49. click(findTestObject("Actpol_Scripts/Date/14 th"))
53. delay(1)
57. setText(findTestObject("Actpol_Scripts/Opsporing/MBES18/10 MBES search module/Bijzonderheden"), Bijzonderheden)
61. delay(1)
65. setText(findTestObject("Actpol_Scripts/Opsporing/MBES18/10 MBES search module/Voornaam"), Voornaam)
69. delay(1)
73. setText(findTestObject("Actpol_Scripts/Opsporing/MBES18/10 MBES search module/Achternaam"), Achternaam)
77. delay(1)
81. setText(findTestObject("Actpol_Scripts/Opsporing/MBES18/10 MBES search module/Geboortedatum textbox"), Geboortedatum)
85. delay(2)
89. click(findTestObject("Actpol_Scripts/Opsporing/MBES18/10 MBES search module/Filter"))
93. delay(1)
97. scrollToPosition(10, 7)
101. delay(1)
105. log = new com.kms.katalon.core.logging.KeywordLogger()
109. log.logInfo(getText(findTestObject("Actpol_Scripts/Opsporing/MBES18/10 MBES search module/Datum Incident get text")))
113. delay(1)
117. click(findTestObject("Actpol_Scripts/Opsporing/MBES18/10 MBES search module/resetform"))
121. delay(1)
125. comment("Checking combinations Search module")
129. delay(1)
133. comment("Checking Datum Incident  and Bijzonderheden")
137. click(findTestObject("Actpol_Scripts/Opsporing/MBES18/10 MBES search module/Datum Incident Calender icon"))
141. delay(2)
145. selectOptionByLabel(findTestObject("Actpol_Scripts/Monthyear/Leftmonth"), "sep", false)
149. delay(1)
153. selectOptionByLabel(findTestObject("Actpol_Scripts/Monthyear/Leftyear"), "2019", false)
157. delay(1)
161. click(findTestObject("Actpol_Scripts/Date/14 th"))
165. delay(1)
169. setText(findTestObject("Actpol_Scripts/Opsporing/MBES18/10 MBES search module/Bijzonderheden"), Bijzonderheden)
173. delay(2)
177. click(findTestObject("Actpol_Scripts/Opsporing/MBES18/10 MBES search module/Filter"))
181. delay(1)
185. scrollToPosition(10, 7)
189. delay(1)
193. log.logInfo(getText(findTestObject("Actpol_Scripts/Opsporing/MBES18/10 MBES search module/Datum Incident get text")))
197. delay(1)
201. delay(1)
205. click(findTestObject("Actpol_Scripts/Opsporing/MBES18/10 MBES search module/resetform"))
209. delay(1)
213. delay(1)
217. comment("Checking Datum Incident  and Voornaam")
221. delay(1)
225. click(findTestObject("Actpol_Scripts/Opsporing/MBES18/10 MBES search module/Datum Incident Calender icon"))
229. delay(2)
233. selectOptionByLabel(findTestObject("Actpol_Scripts/Monthyear/Leftmonth"), "sep", false)
237. delay(1)
241. selectOptionByLabel(findTestObject("Actpol_Scripts/Monthyear/Leftyear"), "2019", false)
245. delay(1)
249. click(findTestObject("Actpol_Scripts/Date/14 th"))
253. delay(1)
257. setText(findTestObject("Actpol_Scripts/Opsporing/MBES18/10 MBES search module/Voornaam"), Voornaam)
261. delay(2)
265. click(findTestObject("Actpol_Scripts/Opsporing/MBES18/10 MBES search module/Filter"))
269. delay(1)
273. scrollToPosition(10, 7)
277. delay(1)
281. log.logInfo(getText(findTestObject("Actpol_Scripts/Opsporing/MBES18/10 MBES search module/Datum Incident get text")))
285. delay(1)
289. click(findTestObject("Actpol_Scripts/Opsporing/MBES18/10 MBES search module/resetform"))
293. comment("Checking Datum Incident  and Achternaam")
297. delay(2)
301. click(findTestObject("Actpol_Scripts/Opsporing/MBES18/10 MBES search module/Datum Incident Calender icon"))
305. delay(2)
309. selectOptionByLabel(findTestObject("Actpol_Scripts/Monthyear/Leftmonth"), "sep", false)
313. delay(1)
317. selectOptionByLabel(findTestObject("Actpol_Scripts/Monthyear/Leftyear"), "2019", false)
321. delay(1)
325. click(findTestObject("Actpol_Scripts/Date/14 th"))
329. delay(1)
333. setText(findTestObject("Actpol_Scripts/Opsporing/MBES18/10 MBES search module/Achternaam"), Achternaam)
337. delay(2)
341. click(findTestObject("Actpol_Scripts/Opsporing/MBES18/10 MBES search module/Filter"))
345. delay(1)
349. scrollToPosition(10, 7)
353. delay(1)
357. log.logInfo(getText(findTestObject("Actpol_Scripts/Opsporing/MBES18/10 MBES search module/Datum Incident get text")))
361. delay(1)
365. delay(1)
369. click(findTestObject("Actpol_Scripts/Opsporing/MBES18/10 MBES search module/resetform"))
373. comment("Checking Datum Incident  and Geboortedatum")
377. delay(2)
381. click(findTestObject("Actpol_Scripts/Opsporing/MBES18/10 MBES search module/Datum Incident Calender icon"))
385. delay(2)
389. selectOptionByLabel(findTestObject("Actpol_Scripts/Monthyear/Leftmonth"), "sep", false)
393. delay(1)
397. selectOptionByLabel(findTestObject("Actpol_Scripts/Monthyear/Leftyear"), "2019", false)
401. delay(1)
405. click(findTestObject("Actpol_Scripts/Date/14 th"))
409. delay(1)
413. setText(findTestObject("Actpol_Scripts/Opsporing/MBES18/10 MBES search module/Geboortedatum textbox"), Geboortedatum)
417. delay(2)
421. click(findTestObject("Actpol_Scripts/Opsporing/MBES18/10 MBES search module/Filter"))
425. delay(1)
429. scrollToPosition(10, 7)
433. delay(1)
437. log.logInfo(getText(findTestObject("Actpol_Scripts/Opsporing/MBES18/10 MBES search module/Datum Incident get text")))
441. delay(1)