3. Login to the application
1. openBrowser("")
5. deleteAllCookies()
9. waitForPageLoad(60)
13. maximizeWindow()
17. ACTPOLTESTENV = 1
21. ACTPOLDEVENV = 2
25. ACTPOLKCENV = 3
29. ACTPOLKBKPCNENV = 4
33. ACTPOLKBKMARENV = 5
37. ACTPOLKMENV = 6
41. ACTPOLKWENV = 7
45. environment = ACTPOLTESTENV
49. Selectenv =
53. switch (environment)
2. println(Selectenv = "ACTPOL-TEST-ENV")
6. navigateToUrl(TESTURL)
10. setText(findTestObject("Actpol_Scripts/login/userid"), username)
14. setMaskedText(findTestObject("Actpol_Scripts/login/password"), password)
18. click(findTestObject("Actpol_Scripts/login/login"))
22. getWindowTitle()
26. delay(5)
30. break
7. log = new com.kms.katalon.core.logging.KeywordLogger()
11. delay(1)
17. Mouse over to Generic tab
21. log.logInfo("Successfully logged")
25. delay(2)
31. Click MBES tab
35. delay(2)
41. Click MBES tab
45. log.logInfo("Clicking MBES18 tab ")
49. delay(3)
53. takeScreenshot()
57. log.logInfo("MBES18 module is displayed")
61. delay(1)
67. Get text from the feild
71. log.logInfo("Grid is shown contains columns mentioned ::" + optie)
75. delay(1)
81. Get text from the feild
85. log.logInfo("Grid is shown contains columns mentioned ::" + vlg)
89. delay(1)
95. Get text from the feild
99. log.logInfo("Grid is shown contains columns mentioned ::" + datam)
103. delay(1)
109. Get text from the feild
113. log.logInfo("Grid is shown contains columns mentioned ::" + org)
117. delay(1)
123. Get text from the feild
127. log.logInfo("Grid is shown contains columns mentioned ::" + voornaam)
131. delay(1)
137. Get text from the feild
141. log.logInfo("Grid is shown contains columns mentioned ::" + achternaam)
145. delay(1)
151. Get text from the feild
155. log.logInfo("Grid is shown contains columns mentioned ::" + geb)
159. log.logInfo("MBES18 module a grid will shown in Arrestanten, with the Options Vrnummer, Datum incident, Organisatie,Voornaam, Achternaam and  Geboortedatum.")