1. callTestCase(findTestCase("main/Actpol_Login_testenv"), [:], STOP_ON_FAILURE)
1. openBrowser("")
5. deleteAllCookies()
9. waitForPageLoad(60)
13. maximizeWindow()
17. ACTPOLTESTENV = 1
21. ACTPOLDEVENV = 2
25. ACTPOLKCENV = 3
29. ACTPOLKBKPCNENV = 4
33. ACTPOLKBKMARENV = 5
37. ACTPOLKMENV = 6
41. ACTPOLKWENV = 7
45. environment = ACTPOLTESTENV
49. Selectenv =
53. switch (environment)
2. println(Selectenv = "ACTPOL-TEST-ENV")
6. navigateToUrl(TESTURL)
10. setText(findTestObject("Actpol_Scripts/login/userid"), username)
14. setMaskedText(findTestObject("Actpol_Scripts/login/password"), password)
18. click(findTestObject("Actpol_Scripts/login/login"))
22. getWindowTitle()
26. delay(5)
30. break
5. delay(6)
11. Mouse over to Generic tab
15. delay(4)
19. click(findTestObject("Actpol_Scripts/Opsporing/MBES18/MBES18 TAB"))
23. delay(1)
29. Mouse over to Generic tab
33. comment("Adding all feilds of MBES18 ")
37. delay(2)
41. click(findTestObject("Actpol_Scripts/Opsporing/MBES18/10 MBES search module/Datum Incident Calender icon"))
45. delay(2)
49. selectOptionByLabel(findTestObject("Actpol_Scripts/Monthyear/Leftmonth"), "sep", false)
53. delay(1)
57. selectOptionByLabel(findTestObject("Actpol_Scripts/Monthyear/Leftyear"), "2019", false)
61. delay(1)
65. click(findTestObject("Actpol_Scripts/Date/14 th"))
69. delay(1)
73. selectOptionByLabel(findTestObject("Actpol_Scripts/Opsporing/MBES18/10 MBES search module/Organisatie"), Bijzonderheden, false)
77. delay(1)
81. setText(findTestObject("Actpol_Scripts/Opsporing/MBES18/10 MBES search module/Voornaam"), Voornaam)
85. delay(1)
89. setText(findTestObject("Actpol_Scripts/Opsporing/MBES18/10 MBES search module/Achternaam"), Achternaam)
93. delay(1)
97. setText(findTestObject("Actpol_Scripts/Opsporing/MBES18/10 MBES search module/Geboortedatum textbox"), Geboortedatum)
101. click(findTestObject("Actpol_Scripts/Opsporing/MBES18/10 MBES search module/Geboortedatum Calender icon"))
105. delay(2)
109. selectOptionByLabel(findTestObject("Actpol_Scripts/Monthyear/Leftmonth"), "jan", false)
113. delay(1)
117. selectOptionByLabel(findTestObject("Actpol_Scripts/Monthyear/Leftyear"), "2009", false)
121. delay(1)
125. selectOptionByLabel(findTestObject("Actpol_Scripts/Monthyear/Leftyear"), "1999", false)
129. delay(1)
133. selectOptionByLabel(findTestObject("Actpol_Scripts/Monthyear/Leftyear"), "1989", false)
137. delay(1)
141. selectOptionByLabel(findTestObject("Actpol_Scripts/Monthyear/Leftyear"), "1985", false)
145. delay(1)
149. click(findTestObject("Actpol_Scripts/Date/26th"))
153. delay(2)
157. click(findTestObject("Actpol_Scripts/Opsporing/MBES18/10 MBES search module/Filter"))
161. delay(1)
165. scrollToPosition(10, 7)
169. delay(1)
173. log = new com.kms.katalon.core.logging.KeywordLogger()
177. log.logInfo(getText(findTestObject("Actpol_Scripts/Opsporing/MBES18/10 MBES search module/Datum Incident get text")))
181. delay(1)
185. click(findTestObject("Actpol_Scripts/Opsporing/MBES18/10 MBES search module/resetform"))
189. delay(1)
193. comment("Checking combinations Search module")
197. delay(1)
201. comment("Checking Datum Incident  and Bijzonderheden")
205. click(findTestObject("Actpol_Scripts/Opsporing/MBES18/10 MBES search module/Datum Incident Calender icon"))
209. delay(2)
213. selectOptionByLabel(findTestObject("Actpol_Scripts/Monthyear/Leftmonth"), "sep", false)
217. delay(1)
221. selectOptionByLabel(findTestObject("Actpol_Scripts/Monthyear/Leftyear"), "2019", false)
225. delay(1)
229. click(findTestObject("Actpol_Scripts/Date/14 th"))
233. delay(1)
237. selectOptionByLabel(findTestObject("Actpol_Scripts/Opsporing/MBES18/10 MBES search module/Organisatie"), Bijzonderheden, false)
241. delay(2)
245. click(findTestObject("Actpol_Scripts/Opsporing/MBES18/10 MBES search module/Filter"))